This is the time known as the Great Pirate Era.
A countless array of pirates go to battle across the seas in search of the One Piece,
the legendary treasure left behind by Gold Roger, King of the Pirates.
Monkey D. Luffy, a boy whose body turned to rubber after eating the gum gum fruit,
set sail to become the next King of the Pirates.
As Luffy and his crew conquer numerous obstacles,
they capture the unwanted attention of the world government,
which will use any means necessary to stop them.
Now this exciting!
Can't wait to see what kind of adventure's up next!
With a charted course awash in danger and intrigue,
the crew will cut a path across the Grand Line to the New World.
Separated from the rest of his crew,
Luffy has finally arrived at Marineford to rescue his brother Ace.
Fighting alongside Whitebeard and his associates,
he continues to push toward the scaffold.
Although Whitebeard himself is critically injured,
he entrusts Ace's future to Luffy,
who is aided by a team of pirates forging a path for him.
Stop and listen to me!
What's wrong?
There's a new plan!
I'm either gonna live or I'm gonna die!
So back up Straw Hat with everything you've got!
They did it!
They cleared a path!
We did it!
I'm here!
Grandpa!
Get out of the way!
I'm not moving a damned inch!
I'm a Vice Admiral of the Navy!
I've been fighting pirates since long before you were born!
And I ain't stopping today!
Old man!
You're not my grandson here!
You are the pirate Straw Hat Luffy!
And I'll fight you to the death!
This is the path that you chose to take!
You and your brother alike!
Each on different paths!
Luffy versus Garp!
Come on!
Grandpa!
Let me by!
Please!
Luffy!
Hey!
Kobe!
Stay with me, little buddy!
You'll make it!
How could you do this to my friend?
Kobe looked up to you, Straw Hat!
I'll make you pay for this!
I'm too weak.
I have to get stronger.
Kobe!
You're alive!
Don't scare me!
Where's Luffy?
Who cares?
He ran off!
Wait!
Garp is facing him right at the scaffold!
Are those two really gonna fight?
That's crazy!
Luffy!
I can't believe nobody could stop that kid!
Damn it!
Don't worry about it!
It should be easy to hit him from here!
Take aim!
And fire at will!
Impertinent boars!
Stand back!
Taste my slave arrow!
You!
We almost had him!
Whose side are you on, anyway?
Not yours, fool!
What if you had hit Vice Admiral Garp with a stray shot?
Yeah, but...
I must protect him!
Because Vice Admiral Garp is my beloved grandfather!
Wait, that's not right!
Yeah, that's news to me, too!
Well, he will be if I ever marry Luffy!
And I'm sure I will someday!
She's crazy!
But cute!
The bridge is gonna give out, straw boy!
You gotta move it or lose it!
Whatever it takes!
Almost there!
A pilot...
Has the goal...
To ask a Marine to step aside?
You wanna pass me?
Then treat me like any other Marine you've faced and fight for your life!
What?
Oh!
Grandpa!
This kinda hurts!
Why do you want me to fight these dumb monkeys all day?
It's your training.
Training sucks!
For one, I have to get hit all the time, and for two, I'm hungry!
Don't be a baby!
You're gonna be a fine Marine someday, just like me!
Nuh-uh!
I'm gonna be a pirate!
Marines are all lame!
Huh?
You little punk!
The monkeys hit hard!
But you're even worse, Gramps!
No!
Now, gum gum!
Aaaaah!
You're killing me kiddo!
Hey, you wanna know a secret?
Huh?
What is it?
Hey, you want to know a secret?
Huh? What is it?
Turns out, I'm not going to be a pirate.
Now that's my boy, you finally get it.
Uh-huh. I'll be way cooler than any pirate.
I'll be king of the pirates!
This is Shakes' influence, isn't it?
You're dismissed, ape.
I'm going to teach you to be a proper marine if I have to beat it into you.
Not this again!
The only way you will ever be a pirate is if I'm six feet under, boy!
You're all tuckered out, but I see your stomach's as lively as ever.
Or as noisy, at least.
You probably don't care for me much, since I'm so loud and rough with you all the time.
Can't blame you, really.
But I'm not harsh, because I don't like you.
And I don't want you to be a Navy man for my sake, either.
I just want you to have the strength to do the right thing and walk the right path.
That's my one and only wish.
By the way, I swiped some food from the Navy so you can eat all the meat you want for once.
I figure they owe me a favor and they'll probably think pirates stole it anyway.
Ha ha ha ha ha ha ha ha!
Grandpa...
I'm not hurting you!
Just move!
If you don't strike me dead, then you'll lose Ace!
Shut up!
You can't just cry till you get your way!
I won't show you mercy!
You're a pirate, Luffy!
That makes you my enemy!
Luffy!
Garb!
Oh, my God.
Damn it, this is all wrong. How the hell am I supposed to feel? Pops, Luffy, my friends. They could save me, but they're pushing through a sea of their own blood to do it. I'm sick. These are tears of joy. Even after all I've done, I want to live.
He took down, Garp.
Old man.
They're family, after all. Damn it.
Ah, look at that. I believe he just might make it.
Hmm, change your mind. I thought you said he couldn't do it.
I didn't say he could save Ace. Now that he's at the top, they'll die together. That's all.
Shut your mouth!
You let your guard down.
Off!
Finally, I'm here.
I told you I'd do it!
Luffy? You really are crazy.
Yeah, well...
Hold on.
Take this.
It's the key to your brother's handcuffs.
I got the key right here.
That's great, but how?
What the hell is that?
That's Sengoku's power. I've never seen it.
Damn, he's huge.
Truck a lot of your life, but you're trapped in the palm of my hand.
This is insane!
A gold statue?
That's not something you should have, Straw Hat. Let's fix that, shall we?
No! The key!
Take aim!
Wait until I give the order, but prepare to fire!
Oh, crap! I lost it!
You've dug your own grave.
You're a criminal as well, Straw Hat.
I've had enough.
I will execute the both of you.
Right here and with my own fair hands!
My goodness.
I think I must have passed out for a moment there.
Straw Hat.
What?
Wait!
Three?
Why are you here?
Three!
What is that thing?
Quick!
Protect Ace with the wall!
I'm not losing now!
I've got giant balloons!
Kendo Wall!
What's she doing?
No!
The whole scaffold's coming down!
What happened up there?
Ace is still alive!
This is awful!
I'll make a key!
Get those cuffs off him and hurry!
You got it!
Look, Captain Buggy!
That's where Brother 3 went!
Holy crap!
I thought he high-tailed it out of this dump, but now he's right in the middle of it!
Also, what the hell is he wearing?
No!
Not that one!
This isn't about putting down a pirate!
It's about maintaining the integrity of our institution!
We must carry it out properly!
Wait a sec!
Those are the executions!
No!
Take a sec!
Those are the executioners.
Ba-dam-a-da-da- baik-da-ba-da-ba.
Kaliq!
Excellent.
They said that Admiral Borsalino stops Straw Hat.
They're in the plaza right now.
Oh, no!
I know you can do it!
And you have lots of friends to help you!
Mister 2!
Oh, okay...
That's that!
Now what do we do?
Rescue Straw Hat before its too late!
before it's too late.
Because I'm his friend!
I don't need any other reason!
That's it?
This is it!
The gate's about to close!
We have to go!
So thank you!
Straw Boy!
I'm here!
Find Ace! Save him!
And don't look back!
He wouldn't run away if he were here.
He honored his friendship with Straw Hat to the bitter end.
Get ready and we'll finally put an end to this!
Yes, sir!
Where's the replacement?
What could possibly be taking him so long?
Well, it was short notice and we don't do this very often.
Hey!
You ready?
Fine. Let's move.
Frankly, I couldn't care less about your brother!
I'm here!
Out of respect for my late comrades!
Laugh at me if you like, but here's your key!
Why would I laugh at that?
What?
Fire!
Blow the tippets before they hit the ground!
Here!
Good luck!
Thanks, three!
Damn it!
That doesn't look good!
Luffy!
Hey, Snow!
Brother Three!
That is an ugly way to go!
Those handcuffs are Sea Prism Stone.
Fire Fist's power won't be able to save him.
Pretty sure we got Straw Hat in there, too.
What is that?
It looks like a tunnel of flames!
Ever since you were little, you've never listened to a word I said, have you?
Then you run off and do something crazy!
Like old times, huh, Luffy?
They're alive!
Well, of course!
It's a true miracle!
Hey, I see them!
Look there in the flames!
Let's go!
Ace is free at last, and the pair of brothers are unstoppable.
Although the White Beep Pirates are emboldened by their team, they are the one who is
the captain's captain's captain.
The captain's captain is convinced that their escape will come so easily.
Ace is free at last, and the pair of brothers are unstoppable.
Although the Whitebeard Pirates are emboldened by their teamwork,
their captain is not convinced that their escape will come so easily.
With his eyes on a new age, Whitebeard makes a difficult decision.
On the next One Piece, Ace Rescued! Whitebeard's Final Order!
I'm gonna be King of the Pirates!
Nice to meet you, though!
Here we go...